all righty house is welcome back should open all of my videos with that intro
应该欢迎 所有正常的 房子 用这个介绍打开我的所有视频
I really hate actually when I'm watching a YouTube video and they have the same intro like I don't know they made a
我在看的时候真的很讨厌 YouTube视频，他们也一样 介绍就像我不知道他们做了一个
weird umm animation of their channel name at the beginning of every video but
奇怪的是他们频道的动画片 名称在每部影片 的开头，但
maybe if you had something personal like me
也许 你有个人喜欢的东西 我
manually singing each intro like today we're going to learn about pasting
像今天一样手动唱每个介绍 我们将学习粘贴
images then I well then I probably losing my subscribers so probably
然后我很好，然后 我可能 很可能失去我的订阅者
shouldn't do that but in this video what I'm going to be showing you guys is how
不应该这样做，但在这个视频中是什么 我要向你们展示你们 是怎么做的
to take two images and combine with together basically the equivalent of copying one image such as this and
拍摄两张 照片并结合使用 基本上相当于 复制一个图像， 如本 和
pasting it on top of another image so that's what we're going to do so I'm
将其粘贴在另一个图像 ，这样 的顶部 那是我们要做的 ，所以我
going to take this little girl's head and paste it right in the middle of this
要带着这个 小女孩的头 并将其粘贴在中间
there is no point to it whatsoever but it's awesome just for demonstrating so
除此之外没有任何意义 它只是为了展示它而非常棒
the first thing we need is to make two different objects two different pillow
我们需要做的第一件事是做两件事 不同的对象两个不同的枕头
objects one of this image in one of this image so I'm going to name the first one
这个对象图像中的一个的这一个 图像，所以我要命名第一个
sister why not of course that's image open and the parameter is the file name so sister dot
妹妹为什么不呢 当然那是开放的形象和 参数是文件 名所以姐姐点
it's jpg and for the second one that's actually a ping this one right here and
它是jpg而第二 个是 jpg 其实一个ping这一个就 在这里 和
I'm Way too lazy to type all that so it was actually probably could've type to
我太懒惰键入所有 所以它 实际上可能可以输入
the faster girl dot ping so now we have two pillow objects one this and one is
现在我们有更快的女孩点ping 两个枕头对象一个，一个是
that bada-bing bada-boom pretty easy so far so the first thing we need is we
bada-bing bada-boom 很 容易 所以我们首先需要的是我们
actually say okay we're going to be pasting something on top of this image
实际上说好的我们会 成为 粘贴的东西在这个图像 的顶部
right here so we need to give it the area that we want to paste now we also
就在这里，所以我们需要给它 我们也想要粘贴的 区域
know that this is the image that we're pretty much going to copy and paste in
知道这是 我们 的 形象 几乎要复制和粘贴
but what we have to do right now is a little math so whenever I click on this
但我们现在必须做的是一个 每当我点击这个时，几乎没有数学
implied charm we can see that the size of this is 200 by 200 now I am stressing
隐含的魅力我们可以看出尺寸 现在我强调这是200乘200
this because whenever we paste it on we need to give it the exact coordinates and that area needs to be 200 by 200 if
这是因为每当我们粘贴它 我们需要给它准确的坐标 如果这个区域需要200乘200
the coordinates you give it are off it all then you're going to come across the
你给它的坐标是关闭它的 所有然后你会碰到
area I'm at an error three reason I said area
区 我说错了三个 原因我说区域
is because that's what I'm going to type so since I want to paste in the middle
是因为那就是我打算输入的内容 所以既然我想粘 在中间
and this original image is 400 by 400 the coordinates the post a 200 by 200
这个原始图像是400乘400 帖子一个200乘200
image is 3 right there so again 100 by 100 is a top left
图像就在那里3 所以100乘100也是左上角
somewhere around here and 300 by 300 is right down here somewhere
在这附近，300乘300 是 就在这儿的某个地方
and of course since this is 200 by 200 then this area is going to fit perfectly
当然，因为这是200乘200 然后这个区域将完美契合
so now that we determine the area what we need to do now is we need to take
所以现在我们确定区域是什么 我们现在需要做的是我们需要采取的行动
that original image which is the sister object and we need to call a function
原来的形象是 姐姐 对象，我们需要 调用一个函数
called paste now paste is going to take two parameters the first thing that's
称为粘贴现在 粘贴即将采取 两个参数是第一件事
going to say is okay what are you pasting on top of this sister richer
要说是 好的 你是什​​么 在这个姐姐更富裕的基础上粘贴
well we're actually going to be pasting this object which is this image so we're
好吧，我们实际上是要粘贴 这个对象就是这个图像所以我们是
going to be pasting that on top of it and the only other thing is it asks okay
将它粘贴在 它 之上 唯一的另一 件事是它没问
now give me the coordinates of where you want to paste it okay sir well we
现在给我你的位置 坐标 我想把它粘贴好吧先生
actually just made them right there and well there you go all right so now what we did is we
实际上只是让他们在那里 和 那你去吧 好的， 所以我们现在所做的就是 我们
basically took this sister image and we pasted something on top of it so now if
基本上拿了 这个姐姐的形象和我们 粘贴在它上面的 东西所以现在如果
we just call sister show check this out run main look at that now of course if
我们只是打电话给姐姐秀看看这个 现在主要看看那个， 如果
you look in this file display whatever it's called the file name you can see
你看这个文件显示什么 它被称为您可以看到 的文件名
that this is indeed one image these aren't two separate files and if you're
这的确是一个图像 ，这些 不是两个单独的文件，如果你是
familiar with Photoshop these are the layers this is actually one layer so we took that image and we pasted it in
熟悉Photoshop这些都是 这 层实际上是一层， 所以 我们 拍下那张照片后我们将它粘贴进去
exactly so I'll show you guys what I'm talking about if we said that our paste
确切地说，我会告诉你们我的意思 谈论我们是否说过 我们的粘贴
area was like 334 for the second one whenever we try to run
第二个区域就像334一样 每当我们试图跑
then we're going to get a bunch of problems right here because it says pretty much the area that you're pasting
然后我们会得到 一堆 问题就在这里，因为它说 几乎 是你要粘贴的区域
into is not equal to the size of the object so that's why I kept stressing
进入不等于 的大小 对象这就是为什么我一直在 强调
the math you have to calculate it before I also show you guys later on um how you
你必须 先计算它的数学计算 我后来也告诉你们你们是怎么做的
like right now we'd probably have to take a calculator if we had any weird
就像现在 我们 可能 不得不这样 如果我们有任何奇怪的话，拿一个计算器
size images but I'll show you guys how to get the sizes dynamically and figure
大小的图像，但我会告诉你们如何 动态地获得尺寸和数字
it out like that but you guys probably could already figure it out from the
它就像那样， 但你们可能 可能 已经从中弄清楚 了
toriel so far so I'm just going to stop rambling that is how you take to him
托里尔到目前为止 所以我只是要 停下来 漫无边际，这就是你对他的看法
just paste them together thank you guys for watching and we can subscribe and
把它们粘在一起 谢谢 你们 观看，我们可以订阅和
I'll see you guys next time
我 下次 会见到 你们